videosift.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy

**TLDR version:** We won't won't share your personal information with anyone without your permission unless we are compelled to by law. 

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [support@videosift.com](mailto:support@videosift.com).

### Gathering and Use of Information

VideoSift.com will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the VideoSift.com Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

VideoSift.com may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, or, on occasion, when mailing lists are made available to other organizations. (The occasional provision of mailing lists to such organizations is the only case where such information would be provided to third parties).

For more information regarding VideoSift.com's policies on the handling and use of VideoSift.com's membership list, please see VideoSift.com's Membership List Policy. The extent of such use is always explained at the time a site visitor provides such information.

If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to 'opt-out.' Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to 'opt-out' they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to 'opt-out' on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.)

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. In some cases, we link the information stored in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on this site.

We use both short-term (session) and long-term (persistent) cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our website, for instance so you can comment on the blog and post on the forum without having to log in multiple times. Persistent cookies remain on your computer's hard drive for an extended period of time. By storing your login information, you do not have to log into your account every time you visit this website. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser's help file.

Some of our business partners (advertisers) use cookies on our website. We have no access or control over these cookies. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by VideoSift.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. See "Third Party Advertisers" below.

**Third Party Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, solely in our discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Acceptance of these VideoSift.com Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this VideoSift.com Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

From time to time, VideoSift.com may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the VideoSift.com Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [support@videosift.com](mailto:support@videosift.com).
